<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ud03_2_CuentosHalloween</string>
    <string name="textWelcome">Insert your name</string>
    <string name="textHintWelcome">Insert your name here</string>
    <string name="btnWelcomeName">Next</string>
    <string name="textTitleStory1">Enchanted Forest</string>
    <string name="textTitleStory2">Haunted House</string>
    <string name="textStory1">Deep in the heart of an ancient, forgotten land lay the Enchanted Forest, a place of twisted trees and thick, perpetual fog.
    No one dared venture inside, for the stories passed down for generations spoke of something sinister lurking within.
    It was said the forest was alive, not with life, but with hunger. One night, a traveler named NAME,
    seeking shelter from a storm, stumbled upon the forest\'s edge.
    The wind howled, and the rain battered her, leaving her no choice but to enter the forbidden wood.
    As soon as she crossed into the forest, the air grew still, unnaturally silent.
    The trees stood unnervingly tall, their blackened bark twisted like skeletal fingers, and their leaves rustled in a whisper only NAME could hear.
    She pressed on, feeling eyes upon her but seeing no one. Suddenly, a faint sound broke the silence—a child\'s laughter, distant and echoing.
    NAME’s heart raced, but something in her compelled her forward.
    She followed the laughter deeper into the woods, where the fog thickened and the trees seemed to close in on her.
    She soon found a clearing where an old, crumbling stone well stood, its mouth yawning wide.
    Sitting beside it was a small girl, her back turned to NAME, humming a haunting lullaby.
    NAME hesitated, but before she could speak, the girl’s head snapped around, revealing a face twisted in agony—her mouth stretched impossibly wide,
    her eyes hollow and dark. "You shouldn’t have come," the girl rasped, her voice a guttural growl.
    The trees seemed to close in, the branches reaching for NAME like claws.
    She turned to run, but the forest had shifted—there was no path, no way out.
    The laughter came again, closer this time, not from the girl but from the trees themselves.
    The last thing NAME saw was the ground opening beneath her, swallowing her whole, as the forest whispered its ancient curse:
    "All who enter must feed the woods."</string>

    <string name="textStory2">
    Sabela was a young woman fascinated by haunted houses.
    One day, she heard rumors about an abandoned mansion in the forest and decided to explore it.
    Inside the house, Sabela found a portrait of Isabella, the former owner, who looked very much like her.
    Intrigued, she investigated Isabella\'s history and discovered that she had mysteriously disappeared.
    During her nights in the mansion, Sabela felt Isabella\'s presence and had a dream in which Isabella handed her a letter.
    The letter revealed the truth about her disappearance.
</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>